# James Lee

#### jazz0910man@gmail.com

Passionate and skilled Web & Blockchain Developer offering 8+ years of relevant experience and a proven track record of success in achieving extraordinary results. With a strong attention to detail and accuracy and the important ability to function well in a team setting, James is looking for a Web & Blockchain Developer job within a forward-moving company.





#### Skills

- JavaScript/TypeScript
- Solidity, Vyper, Web3.js, Web3.py, Truffle, Hardhat
- React.js, React Native, Redux (Toolkit, Saga, Thunk), Context API, Hooks, Zustand, Next.js
- Vue.js, Vuex, Vuetify, Nuxt.js
- Node.js, Express.js, Nest.js
- Rest API, GraphQL

- Storybook
- Bootstrap, Material UI, Chakra UI, Ant Design
- Styled-components, Tailwind CSS
- CSS/SCSS/LESS
- Jest, Enzyme, Cypress, React/Vue Testing library
- AWS

# Work Experience

### Senior Blockchain Developer • XFai

- Built the efficient DEX system based on Etherem
- Developed optimized, well-qualified smart contract
- Built user interface based on the pixel-perfect design
- Integrated smart contract into the React site by using web3.js
- Unit/Integration tests using Jest, Testing library, and Cypress

November 2021 - Present

# Blockchain Developer • OptyFi

- Built the DeFi adapter like the bridge that allows vaults to invest in a protocol for executing Opty.fi's network of strategies.
- Built some DeFi adapters on the Polygon and Avalanche network using Solidity
- Interact with DEX protocols including UniswapV2, V3, Quickswap, etc
- Unit/Integration tests using Hardhat, Web3 libraries

July 2021 - November 2021

#### PM & Lead Developer • ProjectAl

- Engaged in Liquid mode development using React, Hooks, Context, Typescript, React-query, Storybook, Styled-components, React Testing Library, and Cypress, Django, Rest Framework, Postgresql
- Built restful api to get statistic data for surveys of project
- Built user interface based on the pixel-perfect design
- Data visualization with Rechart and D3.is
- Unit/Integration tests using Jest, Testing library, and Cypress

# Frontend Developer • Ecotrak Facility Management Software

- Developed a task management platform with React, Chakra UI, Redux Toolkit, Typescript, GraphQL, Jest, Enzyme, etc
- Developed reusable/scalable components with Storybook
- Structured a global Redux store using the Redux toolkit and data fetching and caching layer using RTK query
- Implemented Drag & Drop with React-dnd in the task board
- API integration using Apollo GraphQL and unit testing with Jest and Enzyme

May 2019 - February 2021

#### Full-stack Developer • Allbirds

- Developed an e-commerce platform using Node.js, Express.js, Microservices, Vue.js, Vuex, Typescript, Jenkins, AWS
- Designed micro-service structure and developed Restful APIs
- Did automation tests on developed API endpoints and distributed API documentation among developers
- Established CI/CD pipelines using Jenkins, Github, and AWS
- Developed e-commerce components and web pages based on pixel-perfect design.

July 2017 - May 2019

# Web Developer • WeedMaps

- Developed a delivery logistics platform using Vue.js, Javascript, HTML, CSS, jQuery, Websocket, etc.
- Developed a customer website where customers can track their job status
- Built dashboards for company owners to manage jobs and drivers and automate & optimize routes
- Migrated web pages in PHP into Vue.js
- Implemented real-time location tracking using google maps and web socket.

March 2015 - May 2017

# Education



Apr 2010 - Jan 2014

**Úniversity of Buenos Aires** 

Bachelor of Science: Computer Science